howlifeworks.com 2017-06-24

# How Life Works

**Last Updated: August 3st, 2016**

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the privacy practices of HowLifeWorks.com (“HowLifeWorks.com,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) with respect to the information we collect on our website at www.howlifeworks.com (the “Site”) as well as information that we or our clients (advertisers or publishers) may collect on other websites in which our advertising technology appears. We are a provider of advertising technology and advertisements that blend and appear to be “native” to the content in which they are delivered (these services are described on our Site and are collectively referred to as the “HowLifeWorks.com Features”). HowLifeWorks.com supports industry self-regulation and adheres to applicable industry guidelines. HowLifeWorks.com adheres to Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) principles and guidelines. HowLifeWorks.com adheres to the IAB Code of Conduct, and the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy statement. This privacy statement is effective as of August, 2016.

## What information does HowLifeWorks.com collect?

HowLifeWorks.com does not collect personally identifiable information unless our visitors voluntarily provide it to us. We do, however, collect certain types of information and ask for personal information in certain circumstances, such as when you set up an account. The following sections describe what type of information we collect, when we collect it and how we use it.

In order to use certain functionality of the HowLifeWorks.com Features, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal information, such as name, e-mail address, phone number, address and other information, such as name of the website and the name of the website owner or administrator.

## Cookies

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a website can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many websites use them. Cookies allow website operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor’s individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to enter information in the Site more than once, thereby saving time. We do not receive or record any personal information in the cookies we use.

## Interest-based advertisements.

HowLifeWorks.com, or other parties we do business with, may place or recognize unique cookies or other technologies on your browser when you visit the Site or other websites in which our advertising technology appears. HowLifeWorks.com, or these third parties, may use these cookies or other technologies to collect information about your use of the Site and/or websites and your other online activities over time and across different websites, and may use that information to serve interest-based advertisements to you as you browse the Internet.

Simply check the “opt-out” button and an “opt-out cookie” will be placed on your computer that stops the tracking of Non-PII data through AppNexus.

To learn more about such interest-based advertising, and to opt out of such collection and use, please visit the below links of the NAI and DAA in the US:

NAI – <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>  
DAA – <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>  
DAA AppChoices – <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/>

Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to return to the above websites to opt out again.

## How do you opt out of interest-based advertisements?

If you would like to opt out of receiving this interest-based advertising, you may do so by visiting the [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), [DAA](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and/or by [clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices/). When you opt out of receiving interest-based advertisements via the Site, we will place a cookie in your web browser that identifies you as opted out. Opting out will not prevent you from seeing advertisements, but the Site will recognize your opt-out cookie and will preclude publishers from using the Site to display interest/context based advertisements to you. The choice to opt out is unique to the browser in which you set it and you may need to repeat your opt-out election if you use a different computer or change browsers. Also, the opt-out cookie cannot be set if your browser is configured to block third-party cookies. Opting out via this method does not prevent the use of cookies or similar means that are necessary for the operation of the Site or other legitimate purposes unrelated to serving advertisements. Information may still be collected about your web browsing activities for these other purposes.

Other websites have their own policies in place with regard to aspects outside of our advertising technology, and we have no responsibility for, or control over the information-collection practices of any other website.

## How do we use the information you provide us?

We use your personal information, such as your name, address, billing and mailing address and credit card number, for billing purposes when we charge you for the use of your account. We also will use your email address to contact you when we provide customer support.

In addition, from time to time, we may also use your email address to send you information on updates to the HowLifeWorks.com Features, or if you choose to be included, to alert you to offerings from other companies that we are affiliated with. To opt in to receiving these emails, please see the section below titled **"How do you opt in to receiving communications?"** We will not sell your personal information or send you offerings from companies that we are not affiliated with.

We may also compile and provide aggregated information about our visitors to outside parties from time to time. For further details, please see the section below titled **"Does HowLifeWorks.com disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?"**

We may use the information we collect to tailor your experience through the HowLifeWorks.com Features by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to access your account and submit information to us, and allowing us to contact you, if necessary.

## How does HowLifeWorks.com protect customer information?

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any credit card information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology ("SSL") and HTTPS protocol and then stored into our databases to be accessed only as stated above.

## Does HowLifeWorks.com disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?

Except as provided for below, HowLifeWorks.com does not currently sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any account registration. This information is used to better understand how visitors use the Site, to support related transactions made on the site, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, or other notifications to them. However, we may compile this data in an aggregate form without any personally identifiable information and may provide aggregated data to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses provided it does not include any personal information.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as responding to your inquiries, offering customer service, or processing payments. These companies are authorized to use your information only as necessary to provide these services to us. In addition, in the event HowLifeWorks.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, visitors’ information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Visitors will be notified via prominent notice on the Site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of information of users held by us. If as a result of the business transition, information will be used for a purpose different from that stated, or implied, at the time of collection users will be given a choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

Notwithstanding any other term of this privacy statement, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

Should you change your mind about the information you’ve provided to us, should you no longer wish to receive information from us, or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal data you gave us. For further details please see the section below titled **"How do you change the information we have for you?"**

## How do you opt in to receiving communications?

In order to opt in to receiving email notifications and updates, please access the "My Account" area of the Site and select the **"Please send me email updates and notifications"** option.

## How do you change the information we have for you?

To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for your account, simply go to the "My Account" section of the Site, log in, then modify your details and settings as necessary. Please note that we require some personal information for billing purposes. If you wish to delete your name, telephone number, email address, billing or mailing address or credit card number, you will be required to terminate your account.

## Third party links and co-brand relationships.

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party websites to link to, and frame within, the Site or to display or promote as part of the HowLifeWorks.com Features. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party websites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such websites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the HowLifeWorks.com Features and the links placed upon each of them, and therefore request any feedback on not only the HowLifeWorks.com Features, but for sites each links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).

## Notification of changes.

By visiting the Site or using the HowLifeWorks.com Features, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also read the Terms of Use establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site and the HowLifeWorks.com Features.
